Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5808
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  3/12/86. Compensation, reinstatement, termination of employment.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  3/12/86. Termination of employment, reinstatement, recall.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  4/1/87. Termination of employment, compensation.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  1/12-87 -4/1/87. Compensation, termination of employment.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  1/12/87. Suspension.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  2/11/86 -1/12/87. Contract interpretation, suspension, discipline, compensation, seniority, termination of employment.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  7/15/86. Compensation, medical release/physical exam, hiring, vacancy, overtime, assignment of jobs.
- Temple University, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  1/21/86 - 2/5/87. School's & colleges-reappointment & tenure, promotions.
- Trojan Luggage, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  11/19/84-7/25/85. Canceled case.
- Tucker House (J.M. Nursing Service), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  6/16/86 -10/27/86. Termination of employment.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  6/19/87. Union elections.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1982-1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  6/17/82 - 5/15/87. Medical release/physical exam, reinstatement, back pay, seniority, discipline, compensation, fringe benefits.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  7/27/87 - 6/26/87. Employee's rights.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  7/13/87. Suspension, compensation, reinstatement, termination of employment.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  7/13/87. Reinstatement, suspension, seniority.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  9/17/86. Termination of employment, reinstatement, compensation, recall.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  10/19/87. Transcript & closing argument (Maeser case).
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  10/19/87. Transcript (Maeser case).
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  10/31/87. Transcripts of Sengheiser case: Termination of employment, fringe benefits.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  3/12/87. Exhibits of Ken Caputo case, sales/mergers/acquisitions, Volume 1.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  3/12/87. Transcript of Ken Caputo case, sales/mergers/acquisitions.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  3/12/87. Exhibit of Ken Caputo case. Volume 2 & 3.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  3/12/87. Exhibit of Ken Caputo case. Volume 4.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  9/16/86. Termination of employment, compensation, suspension, medical release/physical exams.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  12/11/86 - 2/25/87. Discipline, compensation, suspension.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  9/15/87 - 12/2/87. Compensation, suspension, termination of employment, reinstatement.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  9/16/86. Suspension, reinstatement, termination of employment.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  7/3/85 - 9/13/85. Reinstatement, termination of employment, seniority, discipline.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  7/9/85 - 7/31/85. Compensation, assignment of jobs, employee's rights, seniority, vacancy.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co. Maeser case depositions. (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Union Pacific Railroad Co. Maeser case: depositions. (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Union Pacific Railroad Co. Manesar case -depositions. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  10/28/85 - 12/3/85. Contract interpretation.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  2/8/85 - 9/14/85. Compensation, assignment of jobs.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  5/18/85 - 7/25/85. Reinstatement, compensation.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  6/17/86. Sales/mergers / acquisitions.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  6/17/86. *File folder #5, case continued.*
- Union Pacific Railroad Co. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Transcript.
- Union Pacific Railroad Co. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Exhibit for Ken Caputo.
- U.S. Army - Fort Meade, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  2/12/86 - 6/1/86. Promotion, back pay, job classification.
- U.S. Government Printing Office, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  12/19/86 -4/27/87. Promotion, compensation.
- U.S. Patent Office Preamble & agreement. (Box 15, Folder 11)
- U.S. Patent Office, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  5/25/83 - 12/9/85. Contract interpretation, arbitration procedure, duty to bargain.
- Department of Air Force, Department of Labor, Library of Congress, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  4/24/86 - Duty to bargain.
- U.S. Patent Office (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Exhibits
- U.S. Patent Office Duty to bargain. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Exhibits which are copies of union & management proposals.
- U.S. Department of Health & Human Services Duty to bargain. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- U.S. Social Security Administration, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  1/24/85 -4/23/86. Duty to bargain.
- U.S. Social Security Administration Performance system appraisal worksheets. (Box 16, Folder 7)
- U.S. Social Security Administration., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  11/15/85. Exhibits.
- U.S. Social Security Administration, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  1/3/86 -6/7/86. Duty to bargain.
- U.S. Social Security Administration, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  11/14/84 -8/6/86. Canceled case & employee's rights case with negotiations included.
- U.S. Social Security Administration, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  7/13/81 -10/1/81. Bargaining unit, union security, duty to bargain.
- U.S. Social Security Administration, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  3/4/86. Preamble & transcripts of duty to bargain case.
- Washington County Public School, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  3/4/85 -4/10/85. Duty to bargain, contract interpretation.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  5/12/87. Seniority. Transcripts; Volume 1.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  8/31/87 - 9/1/87. Alcoholism/drug abuse, termination of employment.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  8/3/84 - 1/5/85. Assignment of jobs.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  2/13/86-3/22/86. Correspondence.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  6/30/87. Transcript.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  6/1/84 - 2/12/85. Vacancy, promotion, seniority.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  4/6/87. Transcripts.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  3/16/87 -8/16/87. Termination of employment, alcoholism/drug abuse.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  1/4/85 - 4/9/85. Termination of employment.
- Washington Gas & Light Co., 1986 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  5/15/86-8/29/86. Transfer, seniority.
- Washington Gas & Light Co. Transcript. (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  7/3/87 - 10/25/87. Workweek, seniority.
- Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority 1/3/87-11/10/87. Workweek. (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Washington Post, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  12/23/85 - 4/25/86. Assignment of jobs.
- Washington Post, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  8/18/86. Transcript.
- Washington Post, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  12/1/83 - 6/14/83. Assignment of jobs.
- Washington Post, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  4/30/86 - 12/28/86. Termination of employment.
- Washington Post, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  7/28/86. Transcript.
- Washington Post, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  8/19/86. Transcript.
- Washington Post, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  1/16/84 - 6/14/85. Training & trial periods.
- West Chester Arms Termination of employment. (Box 18, Folder 9)
- West Chester Arms, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  1/28/86 - 8/14/86. Strikes, termination of employment.
- West Chester Arms, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  6/29/87-11/7/87. Back pay, termination of employment, reinstatement.
- WESTVACO, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  11/6/85-8/11/86. Vacancy. Decision date 5/19/86.
- WESTVACO, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  10/26/84-4/13/85. Correspondence; cancellation.
- Wholesale Drug Corp. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Correspondence; termination of employment.
- Wicomico County Board of Education, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  8/27/86 -2/6/87. Correspondence; assignment of jobs.
- Miscellaneous information on different companies. (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Jacob Seidenberg talks about his career with Mary Cullen (Box 19)
  - Jacob Seidenberg talks about his career with Mary Cullen (Box 19, Folder 1)